[{"answer": "We did a crossword puzzle together, in bed. It was the most fun I ever had in my entire life. Did you hear me? in my life! Y'know? my friend enter", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I was telling you about my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What, you think I'm going to repeat the whole thing now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No everything is not going good. I'm very uncomfortable. I have no power. I mean, why should she have the upper hand. Once in my life I would like the upper hand. I have no han", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "That smells good, what is that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The beach", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hey, what goes on there, exactly", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, ", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, I was really moved, really moved", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, I'm sure it wasn't at you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well didn't you hear that person laughing? I couldn't play. I was humiliated..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Well then, what was she laughing at", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So, I am have to going to break up with you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I, ... am breaking up with, ... you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "OK, I'll think about you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "All the time? ... OK, All the time", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Do you recognize it? ... The beach", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, I'm talking about the beach", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What are you talking about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What about it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "In the freezer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well I guess there aren't any ice cubes", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "That laugh. That's the laugh. That's it. You're the one", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You put a Pez dispenser on her leg during my recital?", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, I, uh, um, wa, wa, What did I do? ... Where are you going", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Pez-Dispenser.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You can't break up with me. I've got hand", "qsentId": 26}]